<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Siebel to Salesforce Contact Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
I want to synchronize contacts from Siebel to Salesforce.

This Template should serve as a foundation for the process of migrating contacts from Siebel to Salesforce, being able to specify filtering criteria and desired behavior when a contact already exists in the Salesforce. 

As implemented, this Template leverages the [Batch Module](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing).
The batch job is divided in Input, Process and On Complete stages.
During the Input stage the Template query Siebel for all the existing Contacts that match the filtering criteria.
Account associated with Siebel Contact is migrated to Account associated with Contact in Salesforce. The matching is performed by querying a Salesforce instance for an entry with name same as the given Siebel Account name.
In Process stage, the template will group the contacts and create/update them in Salesforce.
Finally during the On Complete stage the Template will  output statistics data into the console and send a notification email with the results of the batch execution to configured list of email addresses.
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
<![CDATA[
To make this Anypoint Template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered. All of them deal with the preparations in both, that must be made in order for all to run smoothly. **Failling to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="sieb_src">
		<![CDATA[
In order to make the siebel connector work smoothly you have to provide the correct version of the siebel jars (Siebel.jar, SiebelJI_enu.jar) that works with your Siebel installation.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="run_it">
<![CDATA[

In any of the ways you would like to run this Anypoint Template, here is an example of the output you'll see after hitting the HTTP endpoint:

<pre>
<h1>Batch Process initiated</h1>
<b>ID:</b>6eea3cc6-7c96-11e3-9a65-55f9f3ae584e<br/>
<b>Records to Be Processed: </b>9<br/>
<b>Start execution on: </b>Thu Oct 22 12:05:33 GMT-03:00 2015
</pre>
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_cloudhub">
<![CDATA[
Once your app is all set and started, supposing you choose as domain name `sieb2sfdccontactmigration` to trigger the use case you just need to hit `http://sieb2sfdccontactmigration.cloudhub.io/migratecontacts` and report will be sent to the emails configured.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_standalone">
<![CDATA[
After this, to trigger the use case you just need to hit the local http endpoint with the port you configured in your file. If this is, for instance, `9090` then you should hit: `http://localhost:9090/migratecontacts` and this will create a CSV report and send it to the mails set.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		<![CDATA[
+ http.port `9090` 
+ migration.startDate `10/22/15 23:0:0`
+ page.size `200`

#### Oracle Siebel Business Objects Connector configuration
+ sieb.user `SADMIN`
+ sieb.password `SADMIN`
+ sieb.server `192.168.10.8`
+ sieb.serverName `SBA_82`
+ sieb.objectManager `EAIObjMgr_enu`
+ sieb.port `2321`

#### Salesforce Connector configuration
+ sfdc.username `joan.baez@org`
+ sfdc.password `JoanBaez456`
+ sfdc.securityToken `ces56arl7apQs56XTddf34X`
+ sfdc.url `https://login.salesforce.com/services/Soap/u/32.0`

#### SMTP Services configuration
+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `exampleuser@gmail.com`
+ smtp.password `ExamplePassword456`

#### E-Mail Details
+ mail.from `batch.migratecontacts.migration%40mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `your.username@youremaildomain.com`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job Finished Report`
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
		<![CDATA[
Salesforce imposes limits on the number of API Calls that can be made. Therefore calculating this amount may be an important factor to consider. The Anypoint Template calls to the API can be calculated using the formula:

***1 + X + X / 200***

Being ***X*** the number of Contacts to be synchronized on each run. 

The division by ***200*** is because, by default, Contacts are gathered in groups of 200 for each Upsert API Call in the commit step. Also consider that this calls are executed repeatedly every polling cycle.	

For instance if 10 records are fetched from origin instance, then 12 api calls will be made (1 + 10 + 1).
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This is the file where you will find the inbound and outbound sides of your integration app.
This Anypoint Template has only an [HTTP Listener Connector](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/HTTP+Listener+Connector) as the way to trigger the use case.

###  Inbound Flow
**HTTP Listener Connector** - Start Report Generation
+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migratecontacts` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		<![CDATA[
Functional aspect of the Anypoint Template is implemented on this XML, directed by one flow responsible of excecuting the logic.
For the purpose of this particular Anypoint Template the *mainFlow* just excecutes the Batch Job which handles all the logic.
This flow has Exception Strategy that basically consists on invoking the *defaultChoiseExceptionStrategy* defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>